<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Warwick Student Cinema</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="refreshimage">refreshImage</string>
    <string name="android_studio_android_com">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="android_studio">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="userimage">userImage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="general_info">Warwick Student Cinema (WSC/Warwick Filmsoc) is a nationally acclaimed, student run, professional standard cinema. Using industry standard 35mm and digital equipment, we provide a genuine cinematic experience to the staff and students of the University of Warwick. As one of the largest and most well-known society on campus, we are active nearly every night of term!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_film">AboutFilm</string>
    <string name="image_of_film">Image of Film</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="cinema_for_all_logo">Cinema For All logo</string>
    <string name="warwick_su_logo">Warwick SU logo</string>
    <string name="nextfilm">NextFilm</string>
    <string name="schedule_noShow">There are currently no films in our schedule.\n\nCheck back later to see what films we are putting next!</string>
    <string name="priceInfo">A \"Member\" is someone who has paid to join the Society, a \"Non-Member\" is someone who is a member of the University of Warwick but not Warwick Student Cinema. 5-Film Passes are available to both members and non-members at different prices, offer 5 films for the price of 4 and are stored on your university card electronically.\n\nRates for The AllNighter and any special events will be advertised separately and supersedes any pricing information shown here.\n\nTo join the Society, you must first be a member of the Societies Federation. The advantages of membership are discounted tickets (£3.00 rather than £4.00), plus exclusive members incentives. When you join, you also get your first ticket free.\n\nThe fee for membership as of September 2016 academic year is £3.50. Membership expires at the end of the academic year in which it was bought.\n\nIf you want to join the Society you will first need to join the Students\' Union Societes Federation. To find prices for this, please visit the SU website.</string>
    <string name="advertise_general">Warwick Student Cinema offers a variety of advertising opportunities for societies, student services and other commercial entities internal and external to the University of Warwick. Our rates are competitive as we exist entirely as a not–for–profit charitable service for the members of the University of Warwick. Money raised through advertising is invested into new equipment, maintenance costs and reducing ticket prices.\n\nIf you are interested in promoting an event, a product or increasing awareness then consider the options we can provide. By advertising with us, your adverstisement will be seen by thousands of people who come to see our films, or read our publicity, across the whole of campus.\n\nPlease try to contact us at least one week before your advert needs to be displayed, but we can often accomodate last minute requests. We reserve the right to refuse advertising on any grounds, and external entities should be aware that we may be subject to restrictions imposed by our sponsors.\n\nWSC is the largest society at the University of Warwick, selling over 15,600 tickets in 2011–12 at 186 events, of which 6,998 tickets were free of admission charge.</string>
    <string name="advertise_preshow">We run a slideshow before the scheduled start of all our screenings, where slides are displayed for 15 seconds in rotation. Multiple slides can be purchased but cannot be queued consecutively. We do not offer video advertising on the main screen. Slides must be exactly 1920x1080 pixels and in Landscape orientation, in PDF/JPG/PNG format or on a PowerPoint slide.</string>
    <string name="advertise_lcd_beginning">WSC owns and operates two 42-inch LCD screens, one situated directly outside three lecture theatres totaling over 600 seats, and the other located in the busy corridor leading to these theatres and the rest of the Science Concourse. Students waiting to attend lectures can easily spend 10 minutes waiting directly in front of these displays, with new students coming every hour. The location was recently described as \'probably the best place on the whole of campus\' for screen advertising to students.</string>
    <string name="advertise_lcd_end">Prices are inclusive of both LCD and preshow slideshows and are subject to change. Video advertising is now available for the LCD screens, but cannot include audio.\n\nAll adverts must be static images, exactly 1920x1080 pixels in size, and in PNG, JPEG, PDF or PowerPoint formats.\n\nAdvertisements will be shown in whole-week slots beginning on the day of your choosing. Bookings for multiple consecutive weeks are welcome\n\nTo book an advert or to get a quote, please email advertising@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk.</string>
    <string name="advertise_sponsorship">Warwick Student Cinema holds a sponsorship agreement with an external company each academic year which is negotiated at the end of Term 2. If you are interested in sponsoring us, please contact our President (president@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk) for more information.</string>
    <string name="advertise_joint">We are happy to run a screening in conjunction with another Warwick Club/Society, but these must be organised during the previous term to that of the screening when we plan our schedule. All WSC members will receive an email announcing the opening of planning for the next schedule, after which you should get in touch as quickly as possible.\n\nUsually only two or three joint screenings can be arranged per term, and can be organised financially in various different ways, including an option where we cover all costs, but keep any profit / absorb any loss. We will put your name/logo in our booklet, and ask for you to promote us to your members in exchange.\n\nMore information on this option is available from the Films Officer (filmsofficer@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk).</string>
    <string name="advertise_booklet">Booklet advertising can consist of a variety of different options. We are able to offer half page or full page adverts and space on the reverse side of the "pull-out" schedule at the centre of the booklet.\n\nOur booklets are distributed to the majority of kitchens on campus, and several boxes are picked up by students passing our publicity stand in the Science building. Our publicity has a print run of approximately 9,000 booklets.\n\nIf you are interested in advertising in our booklet, then please contact us with your requirements and we shall provide competitive rates.\n\nPlease note that booklets for the next term are normally finished by the end of the previous term, and you should contact us no later than Week 6 of the previous term.</string>
    <string name="sight">Sight…</string>
    <string name="sight_text">The first thing you should know about Warwick Student Cinema is that we do not show DVDs, Blu-rays or any other home cinema format media to our audience. Only industry standard equipment is used, that means playing real film; both 35mm and 70mm, as well as DCI compliant movies.</string>
    <string name="_35_70"><![CDATA[35mm & 70mm Film]]></string>
    <string name="_35_70_text">Unlike many other cinemas, Warwick Student Cinema operates its 35/70mm projectors mainly using a changeover system. Films are transported on spools of about twenty minutes each. A typical feature will have 6–7 reels. Basically a system of two projectors is used. One reel is played on the first projector and at the right moment at the end of this reel, we switch over to the second projector and so on. This moment is indicated by \'cue dots\' (marks on the film) which appear in the top right hand corner of the film. There are two sets of dots, the first is approximately 8 seconds before the end of the reel and indicates to the projectionist to start up the second projector. The second set, about 7 seconds later, signals the time for changeover. This should result in an almost seamless changeover which you, the audience, should not notice.\n\nNot only are we able to project standard 35mm film but our projectors are also capable of handling 70mm film. We are the only student cinema in the country capable of playing 70mm with fantastic 6 channel magnetic sound as well as the DTS digital format (see below), and one of only a handful of cinemas in the UK that can show 70mm films on a regular basis. This provides an improved picture due to two reasons. Firstly the film is often in better condition as it will have been played far less than 35mm prints. Secondly, because the film is larger the image is magnified less, providing a higher quality than that of 35mm.</string>
    <string name="platter">Platter</string>
    <string name="platter_text">Warwick Student Cinema is also able to operate with a long play system. This involves, in our case, a platter which was kindly given to us on permanent loan by the Projected Picture Trust in 2002. The platter consists of three giant plates, each approximately 54 inches in diameter. The entire film is spliced together and placed on one of the plates. The film then makes it\'s way to P1 (from which it is projected on screen) via a circuitous route using a series of rollers, before going back to one of the other plates. This is particularly useful in the event of one of the projectors failing, an event which previously would have resulted in the cancellation of the film. Also, unlike any other playing system, films can immediately be played again due to the fact that the film uptake is from the inside of the reel.</string>
    <string name="digital_cinema">Digital Cinema</string>
    <string name="digital_cinema_text">Our society is also lucky enough to have a 2K Digital Cinema projector. The renovated Christie CP2000S was installed late in the summer of 2011. The digital projector consists of projector head (which contains the lamp, lens, douser and pixel boards) and the pedestal (which contains the projector server and alternate content processor). The Cine-IPM 2K (alternate content processor) allows us to display content using the projector that the server would not normally accept (non-DCI compliant content). Naturally, our digital projector does not operate a change-over system. Instead a hard-drive containing the film arrives at the cinema and is then \'ingested\' (uploaded) to the digital projector server. This takes about 3/4 the time taken to play the whole of the film. A playlist on the server is then created which includes auditorium automation (lights, curtains…), pre-film trailers and the film of course. All that needs to be done by the projectionist on the night is to then hit play!</string>
    <string name="sound">…and Sound</string>
    <string name="sound_text">The picture is only half of the cinema experience, the other being the sound. Warwick Student Cinema is able to play all industry standard cinema sound formats including all three major digital systems: Dolby Digital, Digital Theatre Systems (DTS) and Sony Dynamical Digital Sound (SDDS) as well as the older analogue formats: the single channel mono as well as the stereo and analogue surround sound Dolby A and Dolby SR. Digital films all have a standard digital sound format. Our cinema can play up to 5.1 surround: left, centre and right channels provide precise and clear positioning of dialogue, separate left and right surround channels help provide the feeling of immersion in the sound and give general atmosphere and lastly a subwoofer/bass effects channel produces extra strong bass sounds which are particularly audible in action and special effects sequences. The sound readers pick up the information on the film print and send this to the CP500 which can decode the Mono, Dolby A, Dolby SR and Dolby Digital formats. Once decoded, if need be, it converts the digital signals into analogue signals which are then split into the separate channels which are themselves sent to the corresponding amp. The amps then amplify the signals before sending them to the designated speakers in the auditorium. The DTS and SDDS systems both consist of separate readers (that are bolted onto the Vic 8 projectors) and processors. Once processed the information is then sent to the CP500 which does its usual magic. The Digital projector also sends a digital signal to the CP500 which is converted into an analogue signal. But it is not just a crisp picture and clear sound that makes Warwick Student Cinema what it is today. All of this equipment would be useless if it wasn\'t for the steady stream of dedicated technicians who maintain the equipment and the projectionists who run it. These people all give up their time to first be trained and then in turn train the next generations.</string>
    <string name="technical_specifications">Technical Specifications</string>
    <string name="technical_specifications_text">2x Cinemeccanica Victoria 8 35/70mm Projectors\n1x Christie CP2000S Digital Cinema Projector\n1x Christie Cine-IPM 2K\n1x DTS 6-D Digital Sound Processor and DTS readers for 35 and 70mm\n1x Dolby CP500/70 Digital Sound Processor and 2x CAT689 Dolby CP500 Remotes\n2x Dolby/Cinemeccanica Reverse Scan Analogue/Digital Readers\n1x Dolby DMA8+ Digital Media Adapter\n1x Sony DFP-D2000 Digital SDDS Sound Processor\n2x Sony DFP-R2000 Digital SDDS Penthouse Readers\n7x QSC ISA450, 1x QSC ISA750 Profession Amplifiers (giving 7000 - 8000 Watts)\n3x JBL Loudspeaker Stacks for Left, Centre and Right\n2x JBL 4645B and 1x JBL 4645 Subwoofer Loudspeakers\n8x JBL 8340a Surround Loudspeakers Output rating (250w Continuous Pink Noise per speaker)\n4x Wharfedale Diamond 7.1 Monitor Loudspeakers\n1x Marantz CD-36 CD Player and 1x Sony MDSJ320 MiniDisc player\n1x Cinnemeccanica Electric Rewinding Bench\n1x Philips ST-270 platter\n1x Component Engineering MS100 Booth Monitor Panel Unit\n\nDolby Digital and DTS equipment installed by Bell Theatre Services, Ltd.\nAdditional audio equipment supplied by Sound Associates.\nLamps supplied by Jack Roe (CS)\nElectronics and other similar equipment from RS Components Ltd.\nDolby and the Double-D symbol are trademarks of Dolby Laboratories Licensing Corporation.\nPlatter kindly loaned by the Projected Picture Trust.\nSony Dynamic Digital Sound (SDDS) Equipment kindly supplied on permanent loan by Sony UK.\nDigital Projector and Dolby DMA8+ supplied and installed by Arts Alliance Media.</string>
    <string name="tech_authors">Originally by Amanda Window (Technical Team), updated by Timothy Green (Chief Projectionist 2011-12)\n\nLast edited: Thu Sep 22 14:33:27 BST 2011</string>
    <string name="faq_who_title">Who are Warwick Student Cinema?</string>
    <string name="faq_who_text">WSC is the largest society on campus and is a cinema run by students, for the members and guests of Warwick University. We show a wide variety of films from Hollywood blockbusters a few months after their initial release, to the more obscure artistic films that didn\'t get the cinema release they deserved, and the classics that you want to see again.</string>
    <string name="faq_where_title">Where do you show films?</string>
    <string name="faq_where_text">Films are screened in Lecture Theatre 3 on the Science Concourse. This is situated over the bridge from the library</string>
    <string name="faq_howMany_title">How often do you show films?</string>
    <string name="faq_howMany_text">There are screenings on five or six nights each week with two shows on some nights. For more information, please go to the menu and select \"Schedule\"</string>
    <string name="faq_whatFilms_title">How do I know what films are to be shown?</string>
    <string name="faq_whatFilms_text">Posters showing all of the films scheduled for a term and booklets featuring reviews of all these films are available free from various pickup points across campus and at the ticket desk before films. The Film Schedule is always available on this website and in the schedule screen in this app.</string>
    <string name="faq_whereBuy_title">Where can I buy a ticket?</string>
    <string name="faq_whereBuy_text">Tickets are available in the science concourse corridor leading up to Lecture Theatre 3 from 20 minutes before the film starts. In order to get a good seat and to allow the show to start promptly please arrive in good time. Tickets are sold on a first come first served basis.</string>
    <string name="faq_howMuch_title">How much does it cost to watch a film?</string>
    <string name="faq_howMuch_text">Ticket prices for standard screenings can be found in the \"Prices\" section in the drop-down menu above. Special event prices such as for The Allnighter are set per event and will be publicised around the event.\n\nTo become a member of the Society costs £3.50 and includes one free standard film.\n\nEvery member of the University may bring one external guest to each screening subject to the Guest ticket price.</string>
    <string name="faq_howMuchMembership_title">How much does it cost to become a society member?</string>
    <string name="faq_howMuchMembership_text">Annual membership costs £3.50, and is valid until the end of the Academic Year during which it is bought. In order to join us, you will need to be a member of the University of Warwick Students\' Union Societies Federation - details of which can be found on our Tickets and Fees page and on the Students\' Union website.\n\nIf you become a society member then you will receive one free ticket to any standard film of your choice, this means that if you are a member of Societies Federation you can pay £3.50 to join the society and see a film and get future discounts!</string>
    <string name="faq_becomeMember_title">How can I become a society member?</string>
    <string name="faq_becomeMember_text">Memberships are available on the door and can be obtained when you purchase your tickets. Memberships can also be purchased online using the Students\' Union website and via the Students\' Union reception located in the Students\' Union North building.</string>
    <string name="faq_memberBenefits_title">What are the benefits of becoming a society member?</string>
    <string name="faq_memberBenefits_text">Joining WSC means far more than just getting yourself into films a lot cheaper! If you are a member you are able to further reduce your film viewing costs by buying a 5 film ticket for £10.00. Becoming a member also means you can get more involved with the running of the society and it enables us to inform you of WSC events and news which may be of interest of you (we promise we will not send unsolicited email and the frequency will be kept to a minimum).\n\nWe also run special promotions for society members, more info on the Tickets and Fees page.</string>
    <string name="faq_multipleTickets_title">Can I buy multiple tickets?</string>
    <string name="faq_multipeTickets_text">Yes. You may buy a 5-film ticket for just £10.00 (Members) or £14 (Non-Members) which will admit you (but not a guest or University member) to any five standard films and is valid for the complete academic year. We do not sell term or annual passes.</string>
    <string name="faq_foodDrink_title">Can I take food and drink into the Cinema?</string>
    <string name="faq_foodDrink_text">The use of L3 is loaned to us by the University and hence as one of the conditions of use we must respect and enforce the usual \"No Food/Drink/Smoking\" rule. This is regardless of the fact that these rules are largely disobeyed during the daytime.</string>
    <string name="faq_dvd_title">So do you show DVD/Blu-Rays?</string>
    <string name="faq_dvd_text">No! We show most of our films in the format used by all major cinemas, and we are also fully equipped with every professional digital cinema sound format available today (Dolby Digital, DTS and SDDS) - meaning if there\'s a digital soundtrack to a film, we\'ll be using it! We also have over 8kW of amplification power so the speech on the soundtrack is crystal-clear while the effects sound as the director intended.\n\nWe also have the ability (and inclination!) to show films in 70mm - a format not generally seen outside of the best cinemas in London\'s West End. Whenever we can, we will screen a film in 70mm for its improved picture and sound quality, and we usually schedule a 70mm showing of older films during each of the Autumn and Spring terms.</string>
    <string name="faq_howCrew_title">How can I help out with Warwick Student Cinema (i.e. become a crew member)?</string>
    <string name="faq_howCrew_text">You can help with stewarding, projecting the films, publicity and the IT teams. For more information email us at info@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk or arrive early for a regular screening and tell whoever\'s about that you\'d like to become a Crew member. Please have a look at the Getting Involved section on our website.</string>
    <string name="faq_whyCrew_title">Why would I want to help out with Warwick Student Cinema?</string>
    <string name="faq_whyCrew_text">The reason most commonly given is that if you help out a reasonable amount you are entitled to attend all our screenings for free. However, there is more to it than that. Inevitably, in a society as large as ours (nearly 3000 members) the majority of members are in effect merely customers. Becoming a Crew member of WSC is like becoming an ordinary member of the university\'s other societies (except it\'s free) and gives you the opportunity to write reviews, learn how to work a film projector, write something on your C.V. and most importantly have fun along the way.</string>
    <string name="faq_dearWSC_title">Dear Warwick Student Cinema, will you...</string>
    <string name="faq_dearWSC_text">The aims of Warwick Student Cinema are to promote film interest for educational and leisure purposes. We do not provide answers to specific film queries, though discussion may take place on the forums. Warwick Student Cinema will happily help with queries relating to film societies and we do provide advertising opportunities (see the advertising pagefor more details).</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_visiting_title">Visiting WSC as a Customer</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_visiting_text">Our tills will be open around 20 minutes before the scheduled film start time. Simply head to the library, cross the library bridge onto the Science Concourse (Chemistry Building), and you\'ll see our tills.\n\nFilms are screened in Lecture Theatre 3.</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_post_title">Post / Deliveries</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_post_text">Films should be delivered to the Student Cinema Film Dump, on the Ground Floor of the Chemistry Building. Please use our email contact details below for more information and the access code.\n\nOther deliveries and post should be directed to Student Union HQ:\nWarwick Student Cinema,\nStudent Union HQ,\nUniversity of Warwick,\nCoventry,\nCV4 7AL</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_lost_title">Lost Property?</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_lost_text">Valuable lost property is taken to the Security Gatehouse at the end of the screenings for that evening. Less valuable lost property is taken on a regular basis to the Porters Lodge at the entrance to the Science Concourse. If you wish to email us to query if we\'ve found an item, contact the Chief Duty Manager at chiefdm@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk.</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_email_title">E-Mail Us!</string>
    <string name="faq_contact_email_text">Please check our Frequently Asked Questions before getting in touch.\n\nOur schedule is decided through use of the Film Suggestions part of the website, the Forums and a programming meeting announced on the News, around Week 4 of the term before the one being scheduled.\n\nIf you are a Warwick Club or Society and wish to advertise with us or arrange a joint screening, please see the advertising page.\n\nOtherwise, get in touch with the whole Executive by emailing: info@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk.\n\nCompanies seeking to establish a relationship with us can email the President directly: president@filmsoc.warwick.ac.uk</string>
    <string name="faq_tAndC_tickets_title">Ticketing Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="faq_tAndC_tickets_text">\t\t1.) WSC tickets are valid only for the date and time specified on the ticket.\n\t\t2.)Standard shows will be charged at £4.00 for University staff/students who are non-Members, £3.00 for Members and £4.50 for customers from outside the University.\n\t\t3.) Non-standard shows (e.g. AllNighters, Pub Quizzes) will be charged at a rate decided by the WSC Exec.\n\t\t4.) WSC reserve the right to withdraw offers such as \'Members First Film Free\', \'Members Free Film\' at any point.\n\t\t5.) A Five-Film-Pass (Members or non-Members) allows the customer to pay upfront for five films (charged at the price of four). We reserve the right to withdraw the sale of these passes at any point, but any remaining Five-Film-Tickets will be valid for films until the end of the academic year.\n\t\t6.) A WSC Loyalty Card allows the customer one free film for every four films they pay to see. These cannot be used in conjunction with Five-Film-Passes. For full terms and conditions, see bellow.\n\t\t7.) WSC reserve the right to refuse to refund a ticket once it has been purchased.\n\t\t8.) WSC reserve the right to refuse entry to any customer, and this decision is solely at the discretion of the Duty Manager on the night.\n\t\t9.) Any customer who is late (i.e. arrives after our tills has closed) will be required to pay a late-comer fee, should they wish to attend the film. Our standard late-comer charge is £5.00 for all customers, but the decision on whether to admit late-comers at all, and if so what price to charge them is solely at the discretion of the Duty Manager on the night.</string>
    <string name="faq_tAndC_loyality_title">Loyalty Card Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="faq_tAndC_loyalty_text">\t\t1.) A WSC loyalty card may only be used for the purpose of gaining stamps or redeeming films by holders of a valid Warwick University Card (i.e. students and staff)\n\t\t2.) A stamp will be given upon the purchase of a full-priced WSC ticket (£4.00 for non-Members or £3.00 for Members) or a pre-arranged society social ticket or a Members first film free ticket. Members\' free films, five-film-tickets, late-comer tickets and other free or reduced tickets will not be eligible. Stamps will also not be given for special event (Movie Pub Quiz, AllNighter etc.) or External ticket purchases.\n\t\t3.) Only one stamp can be given per person per film.\n\t\t4.) WSC loyalty cards are non-transferrable and WSC reserve the right to check an individual\'s ticket history to verify that cards are not being used fraudulently.\n\t\t5.) For the Autumn 2013 card, stamps may be earnt at any full-priced film up until and including the final screening of term on 3rd December 2013.\n\t\t6.) Once four stamps have been collected, the free ticket may be claimed at any standard WSC screening in the 2013-14 academic year.\n\t\t7.) Free tickets may not be used for special events (Movie Pub Quiz, AllNighter etc.) or in combination with any other offer.\n\t\t8.) WSC reserve the right to refuse to merge two cards.\n\t\t9.) WSC reserve the right to refuse to add a stamp to a card after a customer has purchased their ticket and left the tills.\n\t\t10.) A WSC loyalty card has no cash value.\n\t\t11.) WSC loyalty cards are not for re-sale or transfer.\n\t\t12.) WSC reserve the right to amend these terms and conditions without prior notice.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_get_invlolved">Get Involved</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_img1">Collage of people getting involved in the society</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_overall_title">All Warwick Students and Staff are welcome to Get Involved!</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_overall_text">Interested in being more active within WSC? Learning new skills? Meeting new people? Discovering the art of running a cinema? Being part of the biggest society on campus? Or just want free films for you and a guest? There\'s a role for you with us! For more information, you can always email the exec, or speak to a member of crew at any screening.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_teams_title">Our Teams</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_teams_text">The success of Warwick Student Cinema and the quality of service we are able to provide for our members is entirely down to members of the Crew who volunteer their time to help run every single show, and look after the day to day running of the society. Without the tremendous dedication of these people, the society would not be able to function! WSC is always looking for new people who are willing to offer their help and get involved with the society. We divide into 5 teams which you can get involved with:\n\t\tFront of House\n\t\tProjection\n\t\tPublicity\n\t\tMarketing\n\t\tIT\n\nEach of these teams has different roles available, plus the head of the team sits on the Exec. Of course, getting involved in one area of the society need not limit you to that role - you can volunteer in several different aspects of the society if you wish, so long as you can find the time!</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_freeFilms_title">Free Films, you say?</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_freeFilms_text">As an active crew member of the society you and one guest can attend any standard screening for FREE!\n\nThe skills you obtain by being involved with the largest society on campus also look impressive to potential future employers, and help you to answer no end of interview questions. Plus, WSC tries to maintain an interesting and active social life including holding our own special events, going to see films, bowling, meals, laser quest, the pub, parties, BBQs and much more, new suggestions are always welcomed!</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_img2">End of year social</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_overall_img2_text">End of Year Trip to Warwick Castle</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_foh_overall">The Front of House team of Stewards and Duty Managers looks after everything related to our audience and aims to provide them with the best service possible.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_foh_stewarding_title">Stewarding</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_foh_stewarding_text">Stewards are essential to the society; without them, our shows would not be possible. Stewarding is also the easiest way to get involved with the society, and come with loads of perks:\n\t\t• Earn free films for yourself and a guest!\n\t\t• Work at the interface of the society and its members.\n\t\t• Meet like-minded people who\'re interested in all sorts of films.\n\t\t• Potentially move on the highly transferrable skill of Duty Managing (see below).\n\t\t• Get to know people in other areas of the society - you might even find something else at WSC that you enjoy even more!\n\nThe main roles for a steward are to sell and check tickets for admission. After that, you watch the film you volunteered for, prior to the optional quick trip to the pub for a drink and discussion about the film!\n\nSo, what\'s the commitment? We ask that all new stewards work three shows within a two week window. This is to ensure you get to learn our ticketing system properly. After that, we ask you to volunteer once per fortnight. All stewards fulfilling this commitment are rewarded with free tickets (including for a guest) to each of our regular screenings.\n\nFor more information or to sign up as a new steward, contact the Chief Duty Manager (chiefdm@warwick.film) who\'ll be pleased to receive your email!</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_foh_dm_title">Duty Managers (DMs)</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_foh_dm_text">The Front of House staff working a show are organised by a qualified Duty Manager (DM). The DM, together with the projectionist, is responsible for the running of that show. At a screening, the DM will:\n\t\t• Train any new stewards on our ticketing system and membership selling;\n\t\t• Perform all relevant health and safety checks;\n\t\t• Liaise with the screening\'s projectionist;\n\t\t• Set up and oversee the tills throughout ticket selling;\n\t\t• Cash up the takings and deposit them at the bank.\n\nThe DM is always on hand to resolve any problems that arise during the show. All DMs begin their involvement with Front of House as stewards before going on to the DM training scheme. Training as a DM requires greater commitment than stewarding, but it is an excellent way to become more involved with the society and learn all sorts of useful transferrable skills.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_proj_overall_text">The projection team ensures that all films are projected to the society\'s highest standards, whereas it is the responsibility of the technical team to maintain WSC\'s equipment to minimise the chance that screenings are cancelled or delayed due to equipment problems. WSC currently operates a changeover system of two Victoria 8 35mm projectors, we also have the capability to use a long play system and have recently upgraded to digital projection as well.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_proj_proj_title">Projection</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_proj_proj_text">Want to get involved in the society in a more technical capacity? Then sign up to become a projectionist! The benefits of being a member of the projection team include:\n\t\t• Free films for you and a guest to all of our screenings.\n\t\t• Learn a dying art! 35mm projection across the world is being replaced by digital.\n\t\t• Get a key to the proj box! This means you are a valued member of our team and trusted enough to use all of our equipment without supervision.\n\t\t• Meet loads of great people equally as committed to the society.\n\t\t• Great to put on your CV.\n\nThe projection team, led by the Chief Projectionist, is responsible for the actual presentation side of all films. Once a projectionist has signed up to a show it is their job to project the film to the highest possible quality, without causing damage to the film or our equipment; thus ensuring the audience has the most optimal viewing experience possible.\n\nThis process starts when the film arrives. Firstly, the films projectionist must properly prepare the print (ideally this would happen several days before the showing). Then the film must be shown properly to the audience. Qualified projectionists will normally take one trainee projectionist for each show and progressively ensure the trainee knows everything they need to know in order to be a qualified projectionist themself. The commitment for trainee projectionists is ideally to cover one show a week, merely so that all the knowledge they pick up is kept fresh. Once projectionists qualify they normally cannot project as regularly, merely due to the number of qualified projectionists.\n\nThe training scheme sometimes has a waiting list (though if it does it is usually not very long). To become a trainee, you must first complete an initial training session - where the basic concepts and equipment are introduced, after which trainees can sign-up to project any show. Crew status (which allows free films to be obtained) is gained after the second show a trainee projects.\n\nIf you would like to get involved in projection or for more information please contact the Chief Projectionist at: chiefproj@warwick.film, who will gladly receive your email.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_proj_tech_title">Technical Team</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_proj_tech_text">The technical team, led by the Technical Officer, is responsible for making sure that our projection equipment is maintained and in full working order. The technical team also oversees upgrades in the equipment WSC possesses and makes recommendations for investments in equipment that would aid the projection team. Membership of the technical team is open to qualified projectionists - this is because their training enables them to have a better understanding and a much greater familiarity with our equipment.\n\nThe technical team has semi-regular sessions where routine maintenance to equipment is carried out. Training is a regular part of these tech sessions as it is important for more experienced members to impart their knowledge to newer members.\n\nYou can read all the technical specifications in the \"About Us\" section!\n\nFor more information, or if you wish to get involved in the technical team, please don\'t hesitate to contact our Technical Officer at: techofficer@warwick.film, who will be more than pleased to receive your email.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_publicity_overall_text">The publicity team are responsible for spreading the good word about WSC in attempt to make more people aware of our great service and programming and, ultimately, fill more seats at our screenings.\n\nThere are several ways to get involved with producing and distributing publicity:\n\t\t• Writing film reviews that will be printed in our termly programme booklet and posted on our website for all to read. This is an especially exciting opportunity for budding journalists to contribute their work to an award-winning publication, or indeed for the casual film lover who would like to offer their slant on Hollywood\'s latest.\n\t\t• Image and title acquisition is a fairly easy way to help out, simply involving finding quality graphics of each film\'s title and some images from the film itself for use in our booklets and posters. Aesthetics are a key feature in any form of successful marketing, and a decent variety of eye-catching graphics help set WSC apart from the rest.\n\t\t• Editing the booklet is a fun way to get a bit creative: designing page layouts using the review, title and image for each film to achieve a high quality level of presentation makes for rewarding work, especially when it is published on the printed page.\n\t\t• Designing weekly posters and fliers lets people know what\'s coming soon to WSC in order to keep the masses informed and interested.\n\t\t• Distributing publicity is essential to getting WSC noticed above all the other activity on campus. We need volunteers to take our publicity to residence kitchens around campus, as well as attacking departmental noticeboards with a staple gun!\n\nYou can do as much or as little as you like, and your efforts will be rewarded with free tickets to our screenings, the opportunity to make friends and have fun at socials, and of course the satisfaction of seeing your work in all its glossy glory!\n\nEmail the publicity officer (publicityofficer@warwick.film) for more information.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_marketing_overall_text">The Marketing Team advertises WSC through digital formats such as our LCD and pre-show slideshows and social networks.\n\nThe Marketing Team works under the Marketing Officer and works closely with the Publicity and IT teams. Responsibilities and functions include:\n\t\t• Creating high-quality advertisements for every film screening to populate our pre-show and LCD screen slideshows, whilst maintaing a consistent, high-quality brand image.\n\t\t• Finding interesting content to keep our social network feeds (Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube) up-to-date and relevant, including writing tantalising summaries of every film.\n\t\t• Editing together trailers to generate excitement for the WSC programme each term as well as big events such as Allnighters. These works of art then get shown to thousands of our audience members before screenings and remain available on our YouTube page for all eternity!\n\t\t• Producing promotional videos to sell the society as a whole, showing the world what goes on behind the scenes. These videos are typically entered into "Best Society"-style competitions and are shown to our potential sponsors, so quality is of paramount importance!\n\t\t• Innovating the way the society is publicised, discussing new ways to utilise technology to increase our visibility. You are encouraged to discuss any ideas you may have on the mailing list.\n\nThere are two specialist roles within the Marketing Team with their own responsibilities. The Marketing Officer chooses who from the Team fills these positions:\n\t\t• Digital Trailers Co-ordinator acquires trailers for all the films on our schedule and converts them into the correct format for playing on our new digital projector, editing them if needed. They must ensure there is always an appropriate number of trailers ready to play before films. They work closely with the Projection team to ensure the trailers are accessible and work correctly.\n\t\t• Photography Co-ordinator ensures that photographs and videos are taken of all major WSC events, and that photos of the day-to-day workings of WSC are kept up-to-date, and that these are organised into our archives. They are the first port of call if anyone in the society needs photographs of specific things for the sake of publicity.\n\nIf you are interested in getting involved in the team, please contact the Marketing Officer at marketingofficer@warwick.film.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_it_overall_text">Whether you are great with computers or can just about browse the web, WSC\'s IT Team needs you!\n\nWe are a group of individuals who are lucky enough to be able to choose their working hours (we are not tied to show times), work with our own custom built systems and work with a lot of new and free equipment.\n\nIf you aren\'t particularly technical, we need individuals who can input data onto our website, tell us what looks good / works sensibly, learn HTML, make new webpages or learn how to build computers - don\'t worry, we are happy to train you up!\n\nHowever, for those with technical aptitude, we divide into two sub-teams - the Website and Hardware groups, each with a maintenance and a new projects responsibility. There\'s always loads to do, and you can get involved as much or as little as you wish. Advances we make affect a large group of people and are therefore very rewarding, and broken systems cause a lot of trouble so we truly appreciate those who give up time to fix them.\n\nDon\'t feel you have to only do IT - if you are involved in another area of WSC, come and visit us, or if you are interested in IT it always helps to get a feel for our systems in their actual use environment!\n\nFind out more by contacting the IT Officer (itofficer@warwick.film), who\'ll be happy to receive your email.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_it_hardware_title">Hardware Group</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_it_hardware_text">We have our own server rack, comprising two brand new bespoke Dell Xeon servers running Virtual Machines, a WSC-built storage server and several University hand-me-down machines. The office contains 3 machines (with remote desktop functionality), we have 4 till systems (including card scanners, receipt printers etc), 2 slideshow computers and the display screens outside the lecture theatre. The servers run Debian, otherwise we have a mix of Operating Systems, with the general use machines running Windows 7 and tills on XP.</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_it_website_title">Website Group</string>
    <string name="getInvolved_it_website_text">Our website provides publicity, crew sign ups (including show rotas), and our own custom EPOS system. With a new website in the works and a mammoth undertaking, it\'s all hands on deck! We currently use PHP/MySQL and dabble with several other languages in order to get the job done.</string>
</resources>